I don't know these kids got so weak I
can't eat white breakage wait residue we
grew up on the white as a white bread of
all time Wonder Bread knows like biting
into a cloud it is so white help build a
strong body 12 wait 12 ways I nobody
could move 12 wait
but Wonder Bread would do that for you
you're my friend sandwich was when I was
a kid
spaghetti and meatball on Wonder Bread
that's enough gluten to kill for kids
I don't blame him I don't blame these
kids though I don't know every
commercial they see is a drug commercial
is n8x right for you ask the doctor do
you need Senate X Senate X may cause
baldness blindness loss of appetite
tooth decay anal leakage that is a lot
to cure runny nose I tell you that right
now
we had drug commercials back in the day
but they weren't trying to kill us
watch this 17 plop plop fizz fizz relief
no needs
why are they so lazy since video games
they can't run can't jump you do this
all day I'll give you a perfect example
how lazy kids are today back in our day
we had a lollipop called the charms
lollipop okay that big back thick you
lick that lollipop man it was good leave
that blogged on for about four days and
the amounts which are red and green
aren't right now it's a good lollipop
yes how lazy they are today they make a
lollipop now there's a battery in the
handle and the lollipop spins around how
lazy can you be
I'm tired I think we were the last
generation that go outside and play
everything we did was outside you ran
around the street until the street light
came on and that was a signal for
everybody to go in the house every game
we play was a running game
hide-and-go-seek
was a running game tag was a renegade so
days you step off the house you in the
middle of the game you didn't even know
you was playing you ever played cootie
617 never somebody would grab a stick
like this and it would rub it around and
a little dog crap like that
and they'd chase you all over the
neighborhood with that thing
you step out the house somewhere with
your cootie sick
[Applause]
so we did that's how we were we ran we
ran in every game we played running game
our CK everybody our CK 17 everybody
again girls run and you chase them if
you catch one you couldn't kiss her
that's right our CK we run catching kiss
you know what you learned as a kid
playing that game the cute girls are
really really fast cuz all the ugly
girls run down the street oh I fell Oh
[Applause]
I always fall in this game just run up
on him oh excuse me gotta go
[Music]
came to meet kids no more you got pets
at home 17 yeah we got a dog yeah we had
a dog me and my brothers we used to get
hamsters hamsters are only a dollar
apiece all three of us could get one and
then we used to play hamster Olympics
never played it get a record player
with the hamster on the record player
first you start at 33 then the 45
there's 78 that's Manny be hamsters
flying all over that room
my brother said gee coz he would dip
there's an Krazy Glue before they put
him on the record player see little
hamsters gone around
Vegas 17 what's a record player hey did
you know they drive Bart comedy has
their own app download it right now to
watch save share clips and watch my
whole special